escnow.com 2016-05-02

# Privacy Policy | ESCAPE

**ESCAPE.s Privacy Policy**

**1.         INTRODUCTION**

1.1       ESCAPE.s website (.ESCAPE.s Website.) is operated by ESCAPE Axiata Sdn Bhd (Company No 240867-U)(.ESCAPE.) subject to ESCAPE.s Website Terms of Service made available at [www.ESCnow.com](http://www.escnow.com/) (.Terms of Service.) and this privacy policy (.Privacy Policy.). Your use of the ESCAPE.s Website or Services constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service.

1.2       This Privacy Policy applies to information that you provide to ESCAPE via ESCAPE.s Website and/or by use of other services that may be provided by other means or media by ESCAPE (.Service.), including as set forth below and as defined in the applicable Terms of Service.

1.3       This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you notice of ESCAPE.s information management practices, including the types of information gathered, how it used and safeguarded and the degree to which you may control the maintenance and sharing of your information. ESCAPE will act in accordance with the current Malaysian legislation on personal information including the Personal Data Protection Act 2010, this Policy and as far as practicable, aim to meet current internet best practice.

1.4       For the purposes herein, all words and expressions shall have the same meaning as in the ESCAPE.s Terms of Service, except where otherwise expressly stated.

1.5       By submitting your information, you consent to the use of your personal information collected by ESCAPE, in the manner as set out in this Policy.

**2.         CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

ESCAPE may revise and update this Policy at any time by posting such revised Policy at [www.ESCnow.com](http://www.escnow.com/). You should periodically review this Policy for changes. Your continued use and access of the ESCAPE Website and Service signifies your acceptance to those changes.

**3.         USERS UNDER 18**

ESCAPE.s Website and service is applicable for parties under 18 years of age. If you are under 18, please obtain your parent/guardian's permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to the ESCAPE.s Website. You are not allowed to provide ESCAPE with personal information if you do not have the aforementioned consent.

**4.         THE TYPE OF INFORMATION ESCAPE COLLECTS**

**4.1       PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION**

4.1.1   ESCAPE collects and uses your personal information (i.e. personal information which identifies you, e.g., your name and postal address, date of birth, gender, telephone and fax numbers, email address, and credit/debit card information; lifestyle) only with your knowledge and consent when you use ESCAPE Website or Services or when you respond to communications from ESCAPE (such as contests, questionnaires or surveys) and other information collected on registration or through surveys.

4.1.2   When you request pages from the ESCAPE Website server, it automatically collects some information about your preferences, including your IP address. ESCAPE uses this for online-billing and to help diagnose problems with the ESCAPE Website and server, to administer the ESCAPE Website and for the purposes set out in Clause 5 below.

**4.2       NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

4.2.1   ESCAPE automatically collects aggregate and demographic information about the use of the ESCAPE.s Website, including most frequently visited pages, number of visitors of ESCAPE.s Website daily, duration of visitors. stay on each page, your preferences and other similar sites based on your browsing (click-stream) activities. This information may include the pages you browse and products and Services viewed or ordered. This information helps ESCAPE to better provide you with a more enjoyable, customised service and experience in the future.

4.2.2   ESCAPE uses the information available to create profiles of the ESCAPE Website.s user base. ESCAPE may provide aggregate profile information of its users to advertisers to help tailor information from the advertisers to your interests. For example, ESCAPE may inform advertisers that it has a certain number of ESCAPE Website.s users that have an interest in a topic and are interested in receiving information about the topic.

**4.3       THIRD PARTY INFORMATION**

4.3.1   ESCAPE does not monitor or permanently store third party information save for the purpose of accounting, billing or record keeping, or unless required by law.

**5.        USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

5.1       Your personal information will be used by ESCAPE or ESCAPE.s contractors, agents or third party suppliers with whom ESCAPE enters into agreement to provide the Service (.Authorised Third Parties.), in support of the purposes stated at the time at which it was given or sought, and/or including but not limited to the following reasons:

(i)         for the purposes of technical administration of the ESCAPE.s Website and service;

(ii)        for research and development;

(iii)       for statistical analysis;

(iv)       for customer administration;

(v)        for profiling service preferences;

(vi)       for finance and marketing operations and activities and/or as required in the provision of our services including but not limited to credit control services;

(vii)      in compliance with any regulatory, statutory or legal obligation imposed on us by any relevant authority.;

(viii)     to service your subscription account ("User Account") and otherwise operate and provide the Service to you including but not limited to creating an ESCAPE membership and an optional wallet account;

(ix)       to support your questions about billing or use of the Service;

(x)        to detect and prevent fraudulent activity;

(xii)      to provide other goods and services by ESCAPE or its designated representatives and/or business partners to you or parties designated by you and matters ancillary thereto;

(xiii)     to verify and process payment when you use the ESCAPE.s Website and/or the Service or purchase goods and services from ESCAPE;

(xiv)     to verify and record your personal particulars including comparing it with information from other sources and using the information to communicate with you;

(xv)      conduct market research of the users of ESCAPE.s Website and Service including the number of users, the frequency of use, profile of users and using such analysis for our business plans, the enhancement of our products and services, targeted advertisements and conveying such information in broad aggregate terms to third parties who have or propose to have business dealings with ESCAPE;

(xvi)     to send you information, promotions and updates including marketing and advertising materials in relation to our goods and services and those of third party organisations selected by ESCAPE;

(xvii)    to comply with any order of court or directive from authorities investigating any alleged offence, misdeed and/or abuse or to enforce any of the terms in the Terms of Service, where such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights or property of ESCAPE;

(xviii)   to ESCAPE.s shareholders, related corporations and affiliated companies for purposes of providing any goods or services to the customer;

(xix)     to payment channels including and without limitation, financial institutions for purposes of maintaining financial records, assessing or verifying credit and facilitating payments of any amount due to ESCAPE pursuant to the Terms of Service;

(xx)      to other service providers or to parties nominated by ESCAPE either solely or jointly with other service providers, for purposes of establishing and maintaining a common database of customers; and/or

(xxi)     to ESCAPE.s professional advisors on a need to know basis.

5.2       Save in accordance with the Terms of Service, Clause 5.1 above  and except as permitted or required under any enactment, law, statute or code, ESCAPE will not use or disclose the your personal information without your prior written consent.

**6.         ACCURACY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

6.1       You are responsible for maintaining and updating the registration information in your User Account with current and complete information. You may access, edit or remove the personal information by signing in to your User Account and following the directions listed therein.

6.2       Failure to provide complete and correct information to ESCAPE as required in the Terms of Service, may result in the your application for the Service being rejected, termination or suspension of the Service.

6.3       ESCAPE strives to maintain complete, current, and accurate information about its customers. Any inaccurate information that is brought to ESCAPE.s attention will be corrected as soon as reasonably practicable upon receipt of such notification.

**7.         DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

7.1       ESCAPE will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. Save as  provided for herein, ESCAPE will not disclose personal information about you to any third party without your consent.

7.2       ESCAPE may from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about particular goods, offers or services that may be of interest to you. In those cases, personal information that may identify you will not be transferred to the third party. All communication whether from ESCAPE or ESCAPE.s business partners will be sent to you by ESCAPE.

7.3       ESCAPE may however, need to work with Authorised Third Parties to provide part or all of the ESCAPE.s Website, the Service and/or other services to you or to perform market research and statistical analysis. In such situations, ESCAPE will share your personal information as is necessary for the Authorised Third Party to perform these services, on a strictly confidential basis. These parties are not allowed to use your personal information disclosed to them except for the limited purpose of providing the particular service for ESCAPE. By using and continuing to use ESCAPE.s Website you are deemed to have consented to such disclosure.

7.4       Notwithstanding Clause 7.3 above, ESCAPE may disclose your personal information about you, your User Account to companies within the ESCAPE Group for accounting or reporting purposes, subject to the terms of this Policy.

7.5       ESCAPE may disclose your personal information to subsidiaries within the ESCAPE Group or other organisations for the purpose as outlined in this Clause 7. ESCAPE may also provide your information to carefully selected third parties whose products or services it believes may be of interest to you. If you do not wish for ESCAPE to disclose your information, please send an e-mail to [service@ESCnow.com](mailto:service@ESCnow.com).

**8.         LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES**

ESCAPE.s Website may contain, from time to time, links to other web sites. ESCAPE is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or of any third party. You should review the privacy policies of such websites when you visit them. This Policy applies solely to information collected by ESCAPE Website.

**9.        COOKIES**

9.1       Cookies are small bits of information that are stored in separate files within your computer's Internet browser. Cookies store information about your activities on a website or other platform. For example, cookies can store your session information for easy sign-in to a website or other platform you have previously visited. They enable ESCAPE to make your use of the Services more enjoyable.

9.2       Depending upon the type of browser you are using, you may set your computers to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to you.

9.3       ESCAPE.s Cookies

9.3.1   ESCAPE uses "cookies" to store and track information about you and your use of ESCAPE.s Website. Unless you have a User Account, ESCAPE.s cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. You may browse ESCAPE.s Website anonymously until your activation of your User Account.

9.3.2   ESCAPE.s cookie and information retrieved from ESCAPE.s cookie is used in line with the uses set out in Clause 5 above and more specifically:

(i)         to help save and retrieve passwords used on ESCAPE.s Website. This way, you will not have to re-enter information upon every new visit to ESCAPE.s  Website;

(ii)        to track information such as the frequency and duration of your use of the ESCAPE.s Website, your click-stream as you go through ESCAPE.s Website, your preferred sites, and help us determine whether you came to ESCAPE.s Website from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement;

(iii)       to analyse the profile of ESCAPE.s Website visitors and users to helps ESCAPE provide you with better service and to enhance ESCAPE.s service; or

(iv)       to personalise the content, banners and promotions that you will see on the ESCAPE.s Website;

9.4       Most cookies are "session cookies," which means that they are automatically deleted from your computer's hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline ESCAPE.s Website cookies if your browser permits, in which case you may not be able to use certain features on the ESCAPE.s Website and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.

9.5       Third Party Cookies

9.5.1   ESCAPE uses other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit ESCAPE.s Website. In the course of serving advertisements to ESCAPE.s Website, ESCAPE.s third-party advertisers may place or recognise a unique cookie in your computer. These companies may use information retrieved from their cookies to provide advertisements on ESCAPE.s Website and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

9.5.2   ESCAPE has no access to or control over thrid-party cookies and such cookies are not subject to this Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy of these third-party websites for details.

9.5.3   If you want to prevent the third-party companies from sending and reading cookies on your computer, you will need to visit each of their websites individually to request that you be removed from that system.

**10.       OPTING-OUT, CHANGE, UPDATE OF AND ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION**

10.1    You will be given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your information used for purposes not directly related to the Service or ESCAPE.s Website at the point where ESCAPE asks for information. If you do not wish to receive our promotional updates you may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line in the email sent or by emailing ESCAPE at [service@ESCnow.com](mailto:service@ESCnow.com).

10.2    If you wish to correct, change or update your particulars in your User Account, by following the steps provided at ESCAPE.s Website. You will need to have your user ID and password.

10.3    You may terminate and deactivate your User Account by sending an email to [service@ESCnow.com](mailto:service@ESCnow.com) specifying your user ID, and expressly state that you wish to terminate your User Account.

10.4    You can write to ESCAPE at any time to obtain details of the personal information ESCAPE holds about you. Please write to: 

[service@ESCnow.com](mailto:service@ESCnow.com) quoting your name, address, user ID and User Account details. It would be helpful if you also provide brief details the information that you need. ESCAPE may charge a reasonable sum as permitted by the Data Protection Act 2010 for administrative charges of providing you with the information required.

10.5    ESCAPE reserves the right to refuse to provide ESCAPE.s visitors with a copy of their personal information by providing a written explanation for such refusal.

**11.      SECURITY**

11.1    The Internet is not a secure medium, and communications over the Internet may be subject to third-party interception. ESCAPE shall not accept responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal information, save in accordance with the Terms of Service.

11.2    ESCAPE has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect your personal information from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors, who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal information.

11.3    While ESCAPE cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur; ESCAPE shall use reasonable endeavours to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

11.4    Personal information that ESCAPE collects from you will be stored and backed up securely in an environmentally-controlled location which shall be accessible by  ESCAPE.s authorised personnel.

11.5    You must remember to log off from your User Account and close the browser window after use to prevent access by unauthorised parties. You must not, at any time, divulge your user ID and password to any third party.

**12.       TRANSFERRING YOUR INFORMATION OUTSIDE OF MALAYSIA**

It may be necessary to transfer your personal information to other group companies or service providers located in countries outside Malaysia. This may happen where ESCAPE.s servers or suppliers and service providers are based outside Malaysia or where you use the ESCAPE.s and/or Service from countries outside Malaysia. In these instances ESCAPE will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights are respected in accordance with this Policy.

**13.       CONTACTING ESCAPE**

If you have any questions about this Policy or your dealings with the ESCAPE.s Website, please write to [service@ESCnow.com](mailto:service@ESCnow.com).
